i'm six foot six where are my big guys
six two or taller clapping because i
guess very tall
thank you sir down front because we
never got to do that when we were kids
did we
tall guy tries to sit in front at school
yeah get in the back
but i can't see the board you're just
gonna play sports you don't need to read
then we don't turn pro and it's just a
life of not fitting anywhere isn't it
so on the flip side where are my little
tiny women five three or shorter little
tiny things where are you yeah
lila all of them down front no shame how
tall are you ma'am
five three and you say it or you say it
with pride i like that you know why
cause short women are always cool with
being short
short men are not always cool with me
and short
no no it isn't your fault story guys i
don't blame you we treat you differently
as a society
you meet a little tiny woman you think
yeah that's kind of hot you meet a
little tiny man you think he's gonna
start a fight
anyone have that friend growing up keep
your eye on napoleon that's his second
beer
he's gonna start something we gotta
finish
you ever do this one in the passenger
seat of a car put your feet up on the
dashboard and take a nap
there are other people answering for you
by the way they're short women it's such
a you know that's a pipe dream for me
and these guys we've never
you know got to realize short women when
you're looking comfortable you're
showing off to people and it's really
rude
we would knee ourselves in the forehead
if we even tried that
because any time your feet are up and
you're sleeping comfortably in a car and
there's a tall person driving
all we're thinking is yeah i hope the
air bag goes off
[Music]
i love when people want to talk about it
too when you're tall people want to talk
about it don't they which would be fine
but they use a voice like they're
telling me something i didn't know about
myself till they showed up
i love that one wow you're tall
just once i want to go oh my god you're
right
i got to quit sleeping in when did that
happen
it didn't happen to me fast though it
was a bad growth spurt did you grow
pretty gradually or did you have one or
two years where you shot up like a weed
yeah 42 years yeah i went from five foot
five to six foot two in one year
last year good lord my 40s how awful no
you know what year most boys get all
their height
is this year your voice is crazy you're
already embarrassed and humiliated
and then mother nature says hey let's
put that voice up above so everybody can
hear it
now people think they're helping you now
you should play basketball yeah
right after i learn how to walk again
let's start there
i don't like that basketball stereotype
because six foot six is tall in life
but it's not tall on the basketball
court it isn't i would still be a guard
in the nba if they didn't have that
talent role
see with tall people we don't band
together nearly enough overweight people
are good at that
fat people show up someplace and they're
in the seats or whatever doesn't fit
them they get together and they sue
tell people we never do that i can prove
to you that we never do that
ceiling fans are still legal
you're like me and these guys those are
medieval torture devices
if you had fat people in your house you
would never think to put helicopter
blades in the doorway
look at some of you grown and thinking
about it all right let's see how bad
aunt ruth wants this cake
no i'm not being mean i'm thinking about
her diabetes
you can make it through the door you get
skinny enough you can have the cake
favorite laugh of the night i am loving
that
no ladies
[Applause]
ladies hear me now let it out whatever
it sounds like
because you know what noise women make
when they try to hold in a laugh
it's always the same one it's smart
always some cute tiny thing that snorts
really loud oh yeah that was way less
embarrassing than you just want to laugh
a woman came up to me after a show once
after a snort and she goes doesn't it
happen to men too
no because what men hardly hold in a
laugh because when we hold in laughter
it turns into a fart
every single time
[Applause]
without fail and not while we're here in
this giant room with people we can blame
it on either
it's a time release that will hit in the
car
you can tell the couples that have been
together a long time
because he'll go and she'll go oh no you
didn't
you let that out here in public or
you're sleeping alone
[Applause]
you're coming on the road with me
oh man
[Laughter]
hey did you know dry bar comedy has
their own app download it now
and you can watch my whole comedy
special and go ahead and leave those
headphones off make everybody else
around you watch it too